I'm sorry, girlfriend. I'm stupid. I'm
so stupid.
It's quite all right, darling. You know
what they say. It takes pain to be
beautiful, and I'm beautiful as a [__]
Okay,
so what do you think of my dress for the
evening? Isn't it giving grape soda?
I don't really care, but I support you.
Well, I suppose one can't expect fashion
sense from a pony who thinks beige is a
personality.
It means a lot that you have chosen me
of all ponies to be your plus one at the
gala. Truly, thank you. It's only
natural I would choose my most dearest
friend to go with me. It's not like I
only chose you because of your ugly ass
bull cut and it makes me look hotter.
They've broken through the barricades. I
repeat, the infected are inside the
city. If you can hear this, do not.
Derpy Jinx, we're all ready for the
gala.
Oh, Twilight, you you invited the
cripples.
Rarity, that's offensive. No, what's
offensive is that I spent 3 hours
cleaning and you tracked in.
Do you like our matching black dresses?
We got them at the Goodwill on discount.
Jinx kept telling me to pick something
else cuz she doesn't want to match, so I
punched her in the face.
You look like you are going to a
funeral.
Ah, that's really funny. Just so you
know, Jinx and I are not dating. I hate
gay people and I don't think they
deserve rights because they are
different.
If you ponies are ready for the night of
your lives, let me hear it.
turns around.
Hold me in your heart tonight in the
magic of the dark moonlight.
Save me from this empty fight in the
game of life. Like a poem by a lady, you
hear the last few words of your life.
[Music]
All night,
where do you think you're going, sweet
cheeks? You still didn't pay the stage
fee.
Cuz I didn't make enough up there to pay
it.
Well, I know another way you could pay
it, black boy. I'm in the mood for some
dark chocolate, if you catch my drift.
$4.
They only ever throw nickels at me every
time. Why? Every pony else gets dollar
bills.
I think only the super attractive ponies
are deemed worthy enough to receive
currency that doesn't hurt.
Hey, we're getting corn dogs with this
money I made, right?
Apple split likes ketchup on his corn
dog.
I am so good at looking out for my pets.
Don't. I hate ketchup.
I want some orange Fanta. Buy it for me
right now.
We can't. Love. These cond dogs were $2
each. You're all out of money.
Can I get deep for a moment?
The floor is yours, girl. I wish I could
provide better in our relationship more
than just by shaking my goods on stage
every Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday,
Thursday, and Friday, and also sometimes
on the weekends.
It's all you're good at, though. Ponies
with schizophrenia are not suited for
real jobs.
[Music]
Can I bring up something else that's
been bothering me? And you have to
promise to be honest.
Go ahead. During Operation Lost Cause,
what happened while I was out? I
remember giving you the permission to do
whatever you wanted with me and then you
slammed me into the wall. I remember
waking up in Saurin's arms after that.
So, what happened? I just want to know.
That's it.
What does it matter? You gave me
permission to do anything and I did what
I wanted.
Look at this. The Canterlot Gala is
tonight. Should we go? It would be a
date.
Enough with the sulking. We're his
toilet at the end of the day. So, make
yourself useful and spread it all wide
open for him here in this dirty
alleyway. You already made him watch as
you put on a show for all those creeps
on stage. I bet he's dying for it.
You're gross. You think that's love? If
he loved us, he wouldn't just stand
there blankfaced all the time when our
head is spiraling. Stop it. Be quiet for
just a second. I told you to stop
carrying these pills around. It's
embarrassing. Do you really want ponies
to think of you as some mentally ill
creep? I'm going to throw these away for
you.
And now he's keeping us off our
medication. That's so hot. Are you
really not going to tell me what you
did?
Will you stand up already? If a pony
walks by, it'll be super awkward.
OMG.
See, that's the thrill of the chase.
Don't ruin it. Braburn, which tie makes
me look more straight passing, blue or
gold? I don't want to get hate crimemed
at the gala.
I can't even get mine on. Appalis and
folk like me aren't used to wearing
these fancy clothing and whatnot. I look
like a rodeo clown.
Then you're going to be the most
handsome rodeo clown at the gala. All
the mayors will be on their knees crying
about how they don't even have a chance.
Are you sure these kind of events don't
usually restrict stallion couples from
even entering?
I'm sure we can get in one dance
together and then we'll be long gone by
the time the Canterlot firing squad
shows up. Hey, you won't be embarrassed
by my new Ollleorn horn I got, will you?
You need to stop being so insecure. Your
horn is perfect. I just got Twilight's
text saying the girlies are waiting
outside for us. Do you got everything?
Yeah, I got the frozen tater tots.
Those little [__] are still frozen.
How are you going to eat them?
They're not for eating. They're for
shoving up my
Applejack was going to come pick us up
with her tractor, but I just got a text
saying Celestia ordered her at gunpoint
not to let us do it because riding into
town on a tractor is too white trash.
So, I just called an Uber.
Now, what do we have here if it isn't
the gays? Seems we're all headed to
tonight's gala.
In rarity? Haha. The gays and rarity.
Haha. I'm planning on being straight for
as long as I can.
You're not alone.
Oh, what a gala. Twilight and Rarity are
really missing out. Where are those
crazy girls?
My butt crack is getting all sweaty and
smelly from dancing all night.
Well, go wash it off in the bathroom
sink, girl. Stick it up in there and
turn on the faucet.
Sorry, I didn't know this one was taken.
Hi. What's your name? My name is Pinkie
Pie. I like balloons.
Oh, hey Pinkie Pie. How is your butt
crack looking? What? Pinkie Pie, you
wanna You want to do it here in front of
every pony? You're a sick little freak.
You know that? Luckily, so am I.
Hey, have you all noticed we kind of
look like the Teletubbies?
Where are we headed this fine evening,
My Little Ponies?
Sombra was the only pony I know with one
of those soccer mom bands.
Why are you all dressed as crayons?
We're going to a gala.
So, do you listen to rap music cuz
you're black?
Big Mac.
Shut up, [__] I want to know.
Golly G, what's wrong?
I don't know. The car stopped working.
A car doesn't just stop working. King
Sombra, did you check the crankshaft
position sensor or see if the ECU threw
a fault code?
Twilight Sparkle. Darling, do I look
like I know how cars work? Everyone out
of the vehicle. I'm calling a tow truck.
It's starting to rain. It's been raining
for 4 hours.
Apple Split has mental health problems.
That doesn't change the fact that it's
raining.
Yep. It's just as I thought.
You found the problem.
No, Twilight babe. That I'm just a gay
man with a tragic lack of car knowledge.
I'm calling a tow truck and hoping we
get a guy with strong arms so I can ask
him to spank me.
You said you were going to do that 30
minutes ago.
I was coming off my poppers when I said
that, babe.
Let me try and hotwire that [__] I hot
wire tractors on the farm all the time.
Did you do it? What do you goddamn
think?
Why?
Because this is a car and not a tractor.
[Applause]
It's working.
Hey, Fluttershy, hop on in home, girl.
What's up, Buttercup?
Twilight, your ass ain't going to
believe this.
All of Ponyville is doomed. They say
can't unlock. Just wait on lock down.
These gayl looking ponies made of cloth
came out of nowhere and are infecting
[__] with some kind of day disease.
Stop, Big Mac. We don't know if
Fluttershy has been infected.
The [__] is human, too.
Where are we going?
Drive all the way to the palace. I must
get in contact with Princess Celestia
immediately.
Give me back my car.
Why did you shoot Sombra? He was chasing
us. He was infected.
No, we stole his car.
Oh, I think I fumbled that one big time.
I'm digging myself out of this.
[Music]
Out of this graveyard.
Nothing but misery and loneliness
under the ground. Surrounded by
skeletons that were lost and never
found.
Buried in good places. But it's time for
me to get out. And it's time to leave
the dead things behind. I'm feeling my
heartbe now. Feeling my heartbe now. I'm
taking myself down.
Ready to stand.
[Music]
An outbreak.
Yeah, and it doesn't seem to be
happening only here in Canterlot. These
mysterious ponies have been showing up
all across Equestria. Their form is made
up of some sort of magical cloth, so we
call them hoodies. When they shroud a
pony with their form, they take them
over mind, body, and soul. Here we've
got a couple of them on display.
Oh my god, is that Rainbow Dash?
Yeah, I found her in the alleyway behind
my castle about an hour ago while I was
taking my 300 p.m. poop. Watch how funny
it is when I smack the cage.
Also, I must confess to something just
as major. But first, Twilight, charge up
your magic and shoot Rainbow Dash. Kill
her.
Wait, Rar, are you sure right now?
Give it your all. Sparkle booty murker.
Nothing came out.
Yeah, I just wanted to embarrass you.
You see, yesterday I did something
really stupid. I I turned off magic
across all of Equestria for the next 48
hours, which means unicorns can't do
spells, and Pagosi can't even fly. We're
all just really lame and useless right
now, like Earth ponies.
I didn't know such a thing was possible.
Well, [__] if you would give me 5
seconds to explain. Last night, I went
to the Ponyville Mall Food Court because
I had a $5 off coupon for orange chicken
at Panda Express, but the fool at the
cash register would not accept it.
Ma'am, I don't actually work here. I'm
just the janitor.
Doesn't matter. I still got a coupon.
That coupon's out of date. It was for
yesterday.
I am God. The concept of time does not
apply to me.
I don't think that's how it works.
I want to speak to your manager. The
manager was on his break, so I sat
outside the store for the next 20
minutes. And then, when I saw him come
out and grabbed the young janitor pony's
ass, I sat down my Dr. Pepper, reached
into my purse, and read a spell to
remove the unicorn manager of his magic
as punishment for denying his god $5 off
her Panda Express order. Immediately
after, I realized I had accidentally
turned off all magic in the world for 48
hours. hat. Then I went to take a
massive poop because it was 300 p.m.
When I got back to my purse, I noticed
the page, which I read off of was
mysteriously missing, torn out. I broke
into the mall's security room with a
gun. Feeling like pity to watch the
security cameras, and I saw that Care
Package and Apple Bottom were doing
something for 45 minutes under one of
the Panda Express tables. care package
came out from under it all sweaty and
ripped out a page from my spell book and
used it to wipe the sweat from his
forehead. Then apple bottom came out
from under the table and licked the
sweaty piece of paper a couple times
before eating it like a fruit rollup.
Now we could just wait 48 hours for the
spell to wear off. But I worry all of
Equestria will be infected by then. The
only way to make a cure now is with
Apple Bottom's DNA. There is some pony I
know who we must send him to. Her name
is Shadow Tempest, and since losing her
horn in a freak accident, she has been
studying magic and the absence of magic.
If there is any pony we can rely on to
make us a cure, it would be her. She is
currently working at Applebee's as a
server in Mayan. Take Apple Bottom there
and have him spit or piss into a vial
and give it to her. She'll know what to
do then.
Princess Celestia, how did Shadow
Temptus lose her horn?
Since you do not have magic, you are
free to take as many of my guns as you
would like.
The hoodies are trying to break in.
How are they all the way up here? Isn't
this the highest point in the castle?
They must be scaling the castle walls.
Christ, these hoodies are talented
little freaks.
Celestia, behind you.
How did you get out of your cage? Get
back in.
Pull the trigger, Twilight. Set her
free.
I I can't do it.
You can.
Can I do it?
Eat le.
Was that Pinkie Pie?
I had no choice. She She was infected
just like Princess Celestia.
Rarity, that was derpy.
Her eyes were facing two different ways.
That's how she always looks.
Oh, I think I fumbled that one big time.
Why did you stomp on the brakes?
There are babies in the road.
OMG.
Zombie baby.
That's my baby sister. What are they
doing to Sweetie Bell?
Some pony needs to shoot them so we can
continue going down the road.
We can't do that. They're babies.
Yeah, but zombie babies.
What a moral dilemma.
Apple split shoot the babies. No, I'm
fine with most things, but I draw the
line at hurting kids.
Really? That's an interesting character
trait I didn't know you had. That's so
cute.
Okay, don't overthink it. Just toss the
boom ball and jump down the head like
it's nothing. No tripping this time.
Should I say something badass yet?
Badass is trying too hard. Be
mysterious. Be cool. B.
[Music]
Who's that?
Well, look who's still alive and
sparkly. It's been an eternity, hasn't
it, Miss Sparkle Sprinkle?
Arena's the evil pony clown.
Saurin, you almost let Jinx their shoot
our new friend. Friendship the evil
cloth pony. I was worried you were the
one behind this when I saw the hoodies.
I thought you changed. You told us to go
out there and find ourselves. Remember?
That's what we're doing. We found this
poor pony who was all by his lonesome
and he became our first friend. He is
not under our control like all the
others. He resents the world. So, we
intend to cleanse it of the things
called ponies so that he may reshape it
in whatever way he pleases because
friends help each other. You taught us
that. You know when I told you too that
you could be your own ponies and not
just extensions of me. I didn't mean
like this. You are mistaken. You did
intend this. You simply failed to define
the limits.
You're talking too much. Can I blow
things up yet?
Our friend is unhappy. Arenos, then
let's make our friend the happiest ever.
Hi
[Music]
Where are you?
These things are endless. We need to go.
Rever apples could go. But the others,
they'll be right behind you. But I'm
staying to hold them off. Every pony
over here.
Move. I'm gay.
I'm gay.
Come, we should go, too. We have the
rest of Equestria to infect so we can
find you more friends like me. My
hoodies will catch up to them.
Yeah, let's go, friend.
Just give me five more seconds. I find
Zalion to be quite interesting.
[Music]
Such a handsome face. It almost makes me
wish I wasn't about to ruin it.
You were going to take yourself out. I
just figured looking at you while I
burned wouldn't have been a bad way to
go.
Casp, you're alive. You're actually
alive. Oh, this is just wonderful.
You've got bones like rebar, cowboy. You
didn't run with the others. You're going
to tell me why.
Brayurn and Applesplit are my cousins,
and they're both bottom [__] so I
wanted to make sure they were both safe
before I was. But even though they're
bottom [__] I know I can trust them
to finish the job. So, I knew if I was
going to be infected, it wouldn't be
forever.
Sentimental country logic. That's almost
wholesome. Ew. I feel like this is the
first unselfish thing I've done in a
long time myself, though, saving you.
And now I immediately regret it. You
stayed behind because of family. Bleh. I
was hoping it was because you're tired
of living and wanted to go out in blaze
like me. I wanted to go together. You
know, I'm hopeless romantic/pyromaniac.
It's complicated.
You didn't try to save me. You threw a
bomb at me
at the infected pooky bear.
Not you.
You just happened to be next to them. I
calculated a solid 5% survival rate. Say
something else, big one, to keep my
interest in you growing. Otherwise,
kaboom, and we're both going to be
glitter.
Do you really think I'm handsome?
Oh my god, I didn't think you'd
reciprocate.
You are quite skilled at keeping me
interested. Say another thing. Go on,
woo me.
Twilight, he's awake.
Start interrogating with violence.
Here, your jacket.
This hideous thing. It smells like
gunpowder and sweat.
If you don't like it, why do you wear
it?
Some pony has been eating beans. Huh?
Because without it, I'm not very
talkative.
Also, it's got so many pockets.
Arenos and Friendship said all that's
happening now is because of you. Is that
true?
Yeah, it's my fault. They're my friends.
[Music]
We don't have to talk right now.
Oh, yes, we are.
Ding, ding, dong. You've seemed to
accidentally kidnapped a friend of ours.
We request that you give him back.
Oh, this just sucks.
[Music]
You came for me
for being its friend. You looked scared
when that thing grabbed you.
I just don't like being touched without
my consent. I've had that happen to me
too many times before. This is my own
little hidey-hole in the multiverse.
Friendship and Arinos made this
dimensional space for me with their
magic so I can hide away and not have to
deal with others whenever I want.
What's your story?
[Music]
I'm tired. We can rest here and continue
in the morning. I think that was the
last of the infected in this area. But
with that being an infected, doesn't
that mean there must be hoodies nearby?
All I'm wondering about is when you're
going to crack open my can of bushes
baked beans so I can have my dinner.
You know, this is the first time you and
I have ever had time to just sit and
talk.
That's true. Are you still in and out of
psych wards?
I don't want to talk about that.
What are you writing? Do you want to
suck the syrup off these beans? The
syrup makes the beans too sweet for me.
Only suck on them, though, and leave the
actual beans for me, please, because
they're my favorite part.
What are you writing?
A letter to Applesplit.
Uh, you know, they're literally like 5
ft away. You could just talk to them.
I could, but it's a touchy subject. The
therapist at the psych ward says it's
easier to express complicated feelings
on paper.
I thought you didn't want to talk about
the psych ward.
I didn't, but then I remembered it's
basically the only thing going on in my
life. I'm in a partial hospitalization
program, which is a posh way of saying
I'm at the psych ward 5 days a week and
free. The other two to take care of my
mail deliveries.
So like mental health jail with weekend
passes. It's like being grounded by the
government. Monday through Friday, I sit
in a padded room, except for when I'm
let out for group therapy to make
drawings out of macaroni. Saturday and
Sunday, I get to roam free with apples
split because I'm too mentally ill for
prison, but also too criminal to qualify
for proper treatment. That actually
sounds like a completely broken system.
Disgusting, isn't it?
So, you perform at the strip club now
and Care Package is okay with it? It
doesn't matter if he's fine with it or
not. It's how I make my living since mom
and dad died. And it's a damn good
living if you ask me. I made six bucks
last week. How much do you make picking
and selling your apples?
About 200 a day.
Oh, I have to go pee.
G Package doesn't really like me going
up on stage. He's possessive.
That's simple jealousy. But I'm trying
to give him the freedom to be who he
wants to be. You know,
I don't want him to think of me as just
someone he does things in bed with.
But I know showing himself off is all
he's good at. And even though our
appetites in the bedroom aren't
compatible in the slightest, I don't
want him to think he has to completely
hide that side of himself away. I like
the attention he gives me. I really do
care, even if I don't understand it.
You don't have to get it to support
them. Sometimes love just means standing
by them and letting them figure out what
they need to do to make themsel at ease
for both of you.
Just do what you want to do. Not
everything has to be centered around
him.
Says the pony whose life totally isn't
centered around Saurin. Isn't that why
you brought that ring? Weren't you going
to propose to him at the gala last
night?
You gave up everything, including the
whole godamn family to be with him. I
get you don't like me being with care
package. So, just be upfront with me.
Care package has problems and you have
problems, too. But
Brayburn, what did Care Package do to me
during Operation Lost Cause? If there's
any pony I can trust to tell me the
truth, I hope it's you.
He didn't do anything.
Please don't lie to me.
I got this ring pop from the Dollar Tree
in front of Care Package's apartment. I
can't afford anything real, so I at
least want to give this to him. But I
need to know what he did to me first. If
he did something bad to me, I can work
through it with him. But I can't find
out later and take the ring back. That
would break my heart so much. I would
die.
He have we finished up yet?
Yeah, I'm I'm almost done. We're going
now. The sun is almost up and soaring
and I heard the sounds of infected
nearby.
I have to pee for just a bit longer.
Go back to Saurin. I'll stay here to
make sure Brayburn finishes his pee
safely.
Okay, I'm done. What are you doing?
Saurin told me her would never tell
Appleplit what I did. I assumed that
meant you wouldn't either.
You need to tell them
why. That would break their little
heart. I'm all that worthless pony has.
They're not worthless.
And they're all I've got, too. Apple
split. And I don't have any pony else.
So, leave us alone, Brayburn. We can't
have the ideal relationship that you and
Saurin have. And I'm not above killing
you for our tranquility. If you won't
tell them that you murdered them once
before, then I will have to.
I'm holding in my hands
knowing you'll come back to me.
Is my baby boy okay?
It absolutely was not me.
Care package board this place up. Apple
split banding up raven.
We're getting out of here. As soon as
you're done, I'll keep the hoodies at
bay for as long as I can. Not until you
tell me what care package did to me
during Operation Lost Cause.
We don't have time for this.
Brayburn's life is on the line. As long
as you're holding out on me.
Are you crazy?
Tell me.
I didn't do anything to you. Apple
split. I would never care package. You
need to
Don't you say anything? Saurin.
Just tell me the truth. Can't you love
me enough to just do that? I do love
you, but that doesn't mean I have to.
Care package killed you
in another timeline. Care package killed
you. I used my alicorn magic to turn
back time to save you. You're alive now
only because of that.
Is that true?
Why?
You said I could do what I wanted to
you. Remember?
[Music]
You little heathen. Get off of me.
I don't want any more to do with you.
[Music]
It's hard to concentrate when I'm the
most turned on. I have been in weeks.
Well, then it's a good thing the both of
us are wearing pants to hide it.
[Music]
So here I am waiting for you.
Got to let you know
for your love. Can't you see?
Where's Apple split? You were never
supposed to know. Surin said he would
never tell you. This is his fault. We
can get rid of him together.
Stay under for just a minute and then
we'll apologize to each other probably
later.
Oops.
We need to go.
[Music]
Let go of me. We're Drew. The moment
right after it happened. I wish I had
never done it. That's why you're still
here. Because I love you more than
anything in this world.
I will fart in your mouth if you don't
let me go.
He inserted his knife into me like 23
times down there. That was so hot.
There's Shadow Tempest standing in front
of Applebees. We can get to it by
crossing through the church over there.
And while we're at the church, we can
pray to horse God and ask him why he
would put us poor ponies through this
hellscape. Wait, you still believe in
horse god even though the apples
disowned you?
I can't just turn off my belief in horse
god overnight. Saurin,
doesn't it bother you though? Like the
horse Bible says you're going to horse
hell just for loving a stallion. If
horse god didn't want me loving a
stallion, he shouldn't have made you so
dang pretty. The hoodies will be up here
in a matter of minutes. We need to jump
across to the other building and make a
run for it.
Jump. That's like 4 ft. You both had
more rides on Big Mac than a carnival
attraction. So don't act like a 10-ft
jump is where you draw the line. If any
pony's got the glutes for that, it's
you, too.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Why are you giving me your gun?
Take it. You'll need it. On a count of
three, jump. 1 2 3.
Saurin, come on.
I can't make the jump, Braburn. You know
that. I'm literally a 50-year-old man.
I'm not leaving you behind.
It'll be fine. We're not saying goodbye
forever.
You and Apple Split will make it to the
meetup. You'll make a cure and then
everything will be fixed. I'm putting
all my faith in you this time, Brayburn.
Good luck. I love you. I love you, too.
I'll see you again soon.
Are you ready to go?
I'm sorry about the falling out you had
with Care package, but I know you can do
better than him.
Did you know what he did?
Yeah.
So, every pony knew but me.
We knew he loved you to an extent.
And there's not many ponies out there
who do. I get it. I freaking get it.
Are you going to be okay?
Why can't I have some pony as good as
Saurin?
Gary package was the only pony who tried
to understand me past all the things I
struggle with. Why would he do something
like that?
I think he does love you, but he has
problems that he can't help, too. It's
best for you that he's gone now.
But I don't want him gone. Brayburn, you
don't know what it was like before him.
Every stallion I've been with would
leave me after one night like I wasn't
worth a thing outside of bed. That male
pony stayed. He's cold and he hurts me.
I'm not blind, but I'd rather be hurt by
him than be touched by some other
stallion who doesn't care. And if he
kills me, why should I be mad? Because
his remorse would at least mean. I
existed. And it's not like I don't hurt
him back, too. And now I left him behind
just like all those stallions have done
to me.
What's this?
Carrier packages. Stupid Lucket. The one
with his dad in it. I pulled it off
during our fight.
[Music]
Sup, [__] Did some pony request a
cure for this horse hellscape we're
living in?
You just shot Shadow Tempest.
Oh, I think I fumbled that one big time.
What do we do now? We're all alone and
there's no pony left to make a cure.
Maybe ponies have been at the top of the
food chain for far too long and it's
time for things to change. Actually,
horses are already far away from the top
since we don't eat meat.
Okay. Is there a bathroom in this place?
I got to go drop turd. Hey, thanks for
comforting me. If there's any pony, I'd
be glad to spend my last days in
Equestria with one who cares.
[Music]
[Applause]
What are you doing?
We're not giving up yet.
The only pony who can make a cure is
dead.
No. The ones who started this can still
reverse it. If we can find friendship
and Arenos, we can make them free all
our friends. We'll just need to use
force.
We're both just gay. We've never used
force for anything in our lives. We
always just lay there and take whatever
the world gives us.
Then it's time for these gays to take
back the world.
You really think we can do this?
If I could survive being plowed by Big
Mac, then I can survive anything.
That makes two of us.
[Music]
Cousin Big Mac, I thought you were dead
leaving us behind like that.
Don't do something like that again.
[Music]
Why are you pulling up your pants?
I didn't.
Did you wipe your mouth?
No.
What were you two doing out there?
That is of no concern to the two of you.
What is, however, is that I know a way
to reverse the infection process without
the requirement of a cure.
Why would you help us?
I'm just interested in seeing what comes
of it. That's all.
It's no coincidence that God left cheese
and cracker. Sorry about that sugar
cube. As I was saying, it ain't no
coincidence that horse gone spared only
his four strongest holy warriors. It is
up to us to spread his radiant light and
purify Ponyville.
I'm agnostic.
What's agnostic?
It means I believe in something. Maybe,
maybe not. Horse god could be real. I'm
not saying he's not. Or he could be
cosmic horse themed hallucination we all
share. I'm spiritually non-committal.
That sounds gay.
I don't know. It just don't sit right
with us. Apple folk trust in someone who
get on their hands and knees before
horse every night so horse god can blast
his love all over their face.
If horse god is all loving, why did he
let my father touch me when I was
little? Okay, we're not here to trauma
dump clean sweep. We all have our
demons.
Who's Clean Sweep?
He's Clean Sweep.
Uncle Clean Sweep.
He told me while we were outside.
That's a stupid name.
[__] you were named after a serial.
While Friendship's hoodies are the ones
who infect ponies, they simply turn
their victims into mindless husks. It is
Arinos with his autistic clown magic who
controls the minds of the infected. So,
I have this theory. I want to put into
motion. We're going to need Apple split
to get infected. As Arinos is a fragment
of Apple Split, Apple Split may be able
to override that mental control and take
control of all those who have been
infected.
What is it? One of your hoodies got
Apple split. One of the halves that made
you and so Apple split is now an
infected. No, he was trying to do
something and I got startled. So, I cut
the connection. Did I mess up? Just keep
playing with your limited edition Selena
Gomez Oreo cookies. You're not infected.
That mentally challenged clown cut the
connection because he was onto us. But I
at least got their location. They're
right down the street.
Can we go kill the onion?
[Music]
The Apple family has come to claim as
there's no use running.
We got one shot at this kitten.
Then let's make it count.
Clean sweep. You brought them right to
me. This is not very friendly of you.
You have betrayed me.
They turned all your guns into balloons.
Tell us something we don't know.
I like the smell of feet. Would you look
at that? Your old pals just couldn't
stay away. They're all dying to welcome
you into the group.
They're climbing up on all sides.
Join the horde and become part of the
true and absolute unification of
friendship.
Saurin
Big Mac, don't you dare. I'm going to
blow you up.
What in the tom foolery? Saurin, you
made a grave mistake turning me into one
of your infected friendship. That's
impossible. You should have been fully
infected. How are you conscious?
Friendship, I'm sorry. I don't get it
either. To control the infected Arinos's
consciousness must constantly stream
through them. But since Arinos themsself
is just a small piece of my own soul,
their mind could never overpower mine. I
realized it immediately. So I hid and
waited for this moment. Because you
gathered all your infected here in one
place. I'm not just free of your
control. I can override it.
Arinos. Yeah. These are not our friends.
Kill every pony here.
Arinos and Saurin are fighting for
control over the infected.
If Saurin is going after friendship, the
rest of us need to go after Arinos. If
Arinos is made up of one half Saurin and
one half Apple Split, I wonder if Apple
split can take control of these things,
too.
Is that Apple Bottom? What in Todd
Nation are they doing?
They're dancing to distract the zombies.
And because they have control over all
of them, the zombies are dancing, too.
Look, joined in.
Oh my god, they are having a dance
battle. Check out the flavor on those
moves that only black ponies have got.
[Music]
I know we weren't like soaring and
Braayburn. Yeah, we were messy, but that
doesn't mean I didn't love you. I still
love you. You were never perfect. You
scared me a lot of the time. But you
were mine. And I don't want this to be
the last way I see you.
Apple bottom.
The pain.
I got you. You're twice as big as me. So
use some of that strength, will you?
[Music]
He can fly again. How strange. Did
Princess Celestia's spell wear off
suddenly?
So does this mean you're not cross with
me anymore?
Trust between us is gone.
[Music]
But we can try to mend things. We're
even now since I basically tried to kill
you, too.
You didn't try, sweetheart. You went
straight for my heart.
Don't make this weird.
You really wanted me gone, didn't you?
Yeah. And after you were gone, I didn't
like it. Even after everything, I didn't
like it at all. Can we make out?
You know, I don't like kissing, but
anything for you.
My magic is back. Mine too was Princess
Celestia's spell undone.
Little homosexual.
Princess Luna. The spell which my sister
casted an apple split consumed has been
undone by true love's kiss, freeing all
ponies of our magic condemning shackles.
How
long ago, Celestia placed a magical seal
on all of her spell books. The laws of
magic state that any and all spells must
have a fail safe when created to turn
them off if they ever get out of hand.
The fail safe my sister placed on all of
her creations is that they can only be
turned off by doing something gay. She
did that because she is straight and
would never dare kiss another female.
But it seems today my sister's
homophobia saved the world.
But even with our magic back, that still
doesn't solve the infection problem.
Shut up, little gay man. I wasn't done
speaking. The hood's infection spreads
by erasing identity. It swallows
memories, warps perception, and leaves
only hollow obedience. To cure it, we
must restore their true selves. And
coincidentally, if the three of us
combine our ollicorn magic, we can help
them do that. Saurin is the oicorn of
space and time. His magic allows him to
reach into each pony's past and future.
He can reminds them of who they were and
who they're meant to be. As the olicorn
of moonlight, I govern dreams and
reflection. My magic lets me illuminate
all that is hidden to give ponies
clarity in their trying times. And most
importantly for this situation, Braburn,
you are the alleorn of gay. In a world
of horses full of mindless obedience,
your magic is the most powerful. It can
make one be gay.
[Music]
friendship. What are they doing? No. No.
Sorry I'm late. Every pony, I was
planning on leaving the Lady Gaga
concert early, but then she started
singing Abracadabra, and you know, I
couldn't leave until that one was over.
Celestia, dear. Oh my god, what's
happened to you? Oh, you're back to
normal. Never mind. Yay. Oh god,
Twilight, I told you to use that
anti-aging cream. You look like [__]
Oh, never mind. You're back to normal,
too. Okay, I I'm going back to the Lady
Gaga concert.
Clean sweep. I thought I could learn
what friendship truly means by meeting
you. I see now you were the wrong test
subject. It's been a party, Saurin, but
we'll be seeing you around.
This was all for you, and so you will be
punished immensely for turning me into a
villain. Come along, [__] I am gay.
You think I know what it means to be
loyal.
Don't touch me. Get off. Get off. Don't
touch me. Get off. Get off.
Saurin, I am sorry, Saurin. It seems I
still have much to learn. Please do not
hold it against me.
Wait,
let me go or you will be pulled into
like the last of time.
I still don't know your story, but I'm
interested in finding out what it is
someday.
So, wherever they take you sweep, I'll
find you. Hold out until then.
I will hold you to it.
The ech of your voice where I can still
hear them sometimes.
I surrender to gravity.
Your graity.
I'm done.
I'm done. Why am I feeling so?
[Applause]
Everything is so cold. I'm a mess. Now
you're gone.
Someone help me. Hold me
cuz I still feel your head. I know that
I'm leaving with ghost.
[Music]
[Applause]
It's a nice night, isn't it?
You got me a Baja blast from Taco Bell.
Only the best for the the pony who saved
the world for a change. I didn't do
much. You were never really even
infected or anything. So, even if I
wasn't there, you would have been fine.
Nonsense. You were a part of it. You
made her straight today. Care package
and Apple Split are skipping the gala.
Does this mean they're not together
anymore?
I don't really understand what Apple
Split and Care Package have. Maybe I
never will, but I guess not every kind
of love is meant to be understood. Some
folks find comfort in places others just
can't. All I know is Applesplit is my
family and I love them. So, if what they
found in care package helps the both of
them find who they are in the long run,
then I'm going to be supporting them. No
matter where life takes my cousin, I
want to be there with open arms to take
care of them when they need it.
I don't want you working at the strip
club anymore. I want you to only show
your body to me. Can you promise me
that?
Only if you stop ignoring all my
advances. If I kiss you, I want you to
to kiss me back, even if you're in one
of your moods. And I want you to sleep
in the same bed as me every night. No
more disappearing to the couch because
you're scared. You're being a bother.
And I want you to tell me when I am
being a bother instead of bottling it up
and going on your late night murder
spre.
And I want you to stop flirting with
random ponies just to see if I'll get
jealous. I already am a jealous pony.
And I want you to stop pretending you're
not possessive. I like it. It makes me
feel wanted. And I want you to stop
calling yourself a handful. Like that's
a warning. I have two hands.
That was cheesy. I want you to stop
hiding my clothes when you're mad at me.
That's toxic.
And I want you to stop looking so hot
when we fight. It's confusing beyond
belief.
One more thing.
We'll each have one more. You go ahead.
I want us to keep being who we are
forever. Like if we ever get married, I
want you to walk down the aisle with a
knife in your boot just in case you
change your mind halfway. And you have
my permission to, you know, kill me and
put on a real good show.
I would never do that to you again.
I want us to get matching tombstones.
That's dark love.
I love you.
I never stopped and I always will.
Saurin, when I was just some cold pick
in apples. I told myself that life was
enough. But since you came crashing into
my life, I've gotten to see places all
across Equestria I never even dreamed
I'd see. You saved me from my family and
helped me rekindle my relationship with
Big Mac after I thought it would be
impossible. You taught me how to forgive
him for everything he'd done to me and
how to be forgiven for the things I had
done. You didn't just love me over the
past year. You helped me love myself.
You and me right here is all I want now.
And now I'm finally ready to ask the
question I've known deep down I'd want
to ask since the day we first met.
Saurin, will you marry me?
I saw the whole world flying with the
Wonderbolts, but I never truly felt at
home until I landed in your hooves. Of
course I will.
[Music]
I didn't
for
[Music]
that
boy.
[Music]
Sneech.
You don't
need
[Music]
foreign
speech.
Sneech.
[Music]
You